cookinglsl.com 2018-06-29

# Cookinglsl.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for Cooking LSL – if you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact me at mira at cookinglsl dot com.

 **Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Hello and Welcome to CookingLSL.

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.  
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Cooking LSL (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

 **Image and recipe use:**

All content on this site is original to Cooking LSL unless otherwise stated.

If you would like to use a photo or recipe on my site, please provide the proper credit to me by linking back to my site. Thank you!

If you’d like to purchase a photo from me, there are several options available. Please contact me for more information.

 **“Personally Identifiable Information”**  
Refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

Information Collection: You may browse the pages on this website without providing us with any personal information. However, if you decide to 1) contact us, 2) sign up for our newsletter; 3) comment on a post. or 4) download an offering from the website, we require you provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). This personal information consists of contact data such as your name and e-mail address (“Contact Data”).

Third Party Online Behavioral Tracking: We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

 **What Personally Identifiable Information is collected (detailed answer)?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

 **How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **With whom the information may be shared?**  
We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

 **How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Cooking LSL is exclusively stored by us. If you don’t want us to store your personal information such as name and email, please contact me at mira@cookinglsl.com and your information will be emoted from our list.

 **What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at mira@cookinglsl.com.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons. Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on https://cookinglsl.com/.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to https://cookinglslg.com/ and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**How does CookingLSL use login information?**  
CookingLSL uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

 **What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
CookingLSL has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.  
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. https://cookinglsl.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

 **How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information.  While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

 **How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at mira@cookinglsl.com

 **Children:**

https://cookinglsl.com/ does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Please contact us if you have any concerns or questions.

 **What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by email and updating our website Privacy Policy.

 **Links:**

This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

 **Affiliate Links (Affiliate Policy) and Advertising:**

I try to provide great content that I think my readers, will find valuable and helpful.

To help make ends meet, I sometimes accept compensation in the form of advertising, sponsored posts, and affiliate links.

The ads on Cooking LSL are provided by Mediavine.

Through the process of serving ads, cookies are used to collect information.

Cooking LSL participates in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

An affiliate program is a relationship with a company that allows Cooking LSL to receive a commission on sales I refer from my website.

I have an affiliate account with Amazon.  If you click on a link in any of my posts and make a purchase, I may receive a small commission on that sale.   Your price always remains the same; it is not higher.

I am always happy when a referral to Amazon results in a commission, but your participation is entirely voluntary.

If you don’t want to participate in the Amazon affiliate program, once you know the name of the product, you can open a new browser window for Amazon and just search for it directly. [  
](https://www.culinaryhill.com/affiliate-advertising-policy/#privacy)

This site also uses Reward Style affiliate links, which help produce a small income to support it.

Third parties may be placing and reading cookies in their internet browser.

 **Ads:**

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information  
when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information  
(e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked  
or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide  
advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These  
companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn  
more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To  
opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

© 2014 – Present  **CookingLSL** , All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials  
from this Site is expressly prohibited.
